<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content="Experienced rape attorney ready to fight for justice and support victims through legal process. Don't face it alone, get help today.Need a defense? Murder attorney at your service. Experienced in handling the toughest cases. Contact us today.Expert drug attorney to defend your case and protect your rights. Don't face drug charges alone, get the legal help you need today.Top criminal lawyer in Los Angeles. Aggressive defense strategies. Proven track record. Call now for a free consultation.Find the best criminal lawyer near you for expert legal defense. Get the help you need to navigate the legal system effectively and protect your rights.Expert legal defense for rape accusations. Trust our experienced team to protect your rights and fight for your innocence. Contact us today."Looking for a murder lawyer? Find expert legal representation for your case and ensure your rights are protected. Contact us today."Expert drug lawyer with proven track record of success. Don't face drug charges alone, get the legal help you need today.Get legal support for domestic violence cases. Protect your rights and safety with experienced lawyers who can help you navigate the legal process.Expert tips on building strong defense strategies for drug crime charges. Protect your rights with the best legal advice.Expert attorneys defending individuals accused of sex crimes. Trust our experienced legal team to protect your rights and reputation.Explore the world of fraud and white-collar crime cases, uncovering the schemes, investigations, and legal proceedings behind these complex crimes.Expert legal defense for homicide charges. Aggressive defense team with proven track record. Contact us for a free consultation.Expert legal representation for federal and state cases. Trust us to defend your rights and fight for the best possible outcome for your case.Discover our impressive client testimonials and successful case results showcasing our expertise and dedication. See why we are the best choice for you!"Learn how to protect your legal rights with expert advice and resources. Don't let anyone violate your rights - take action now!"Discover the ins and outs of the criminal trial process - from arraignment to sentencing. Understand your rights and what to expect in court.Learn how to protect yourself with the best defense strategies against serious charges. Get the legal help you need now.Learn effective strategies for white-collar crimes to protect yourself or your business. Expert advice on defending against fraud and embezzlement.Stay informed with the latest legal insights and news. Get updates on important legal matters and stay ahead of the curve.Get immediate legal help in emergencies. Available 24/7 for any urgent legal issues. Contact us now for expert assistance.The top trial attorneys in Los Angeles offer expert legal representation for your case. Trusted, experienced, and ready to fight for you.A concise guide to understanding California criminal law - essential for anyone navigating the legal system in the Golden State.Learn the essential steps to building a strong defense strategy in just a few minutes with our helpful guide. Boost your confidence and protect your rights!Discover the crucial role of a criminal defense attorney in protecting the rights of individuals accused of crimes.Expert criminal attorney ready to fight for your rights. Top defense strategies for all types of cases. Call now for a free consultation.Need a criminal lawyer? Look no further! Our expert team is here to defend your rights and fight for your freedom. Contact us today!Top criminal attorney in Los Angeles ready to defend your rights. Experienced, aggressive, and dedicated to achieving the best possible outcome for your case.Find a top-rated criminal attorney near you to defend your rights and navigate the legal system with confidence. Trust in expert legal representation.">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/logo.jpg"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Kumbh+Sans:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
.u79d4005e7dd2b5f6bc3df88ad97d13d4 p,.u79d4005e7dd2b5f6bc3df88ad97d13d4 span,.u79d4005e7dd2b5f6bc3df88ad97d13d4 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
*{
font-family: 'Kumbh Sans', sans-serif;
}
.e6f03732293cace11ad76fa46926bddc2:hover{
box-shadow: 0 50.5px 49.9px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
.u79d4005e7dd2b5f6bc3df88ad97d13d4 a{
font-size:16px;
}
.btn-md{
padding: 15.2px 29.9px;
border-radius: 0;
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:7.6px;
padding-right:8.4px;
padding-top:4.5px;
padding-bottom:4.8px;
}
.fbb299c39cef6018c18c17f9f5fe6e216{
background-color:#ffc107!important;
border-color:#ffc107!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
footer{
background:#0a0a0a;
color:#ffffff;
}
.navbar a{
font-size: 18.3px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
.c03456f3b4db1077ee302262110584e68 a,.u79d4005e7dd2b5f6bc3df88ad97d13d4 a{
color:#040404!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
.c03456f3b4db1077ee302262110584e68 p,.c03456f3b4db1077ee302262110584e68 a,.c03456f3b4db1077ee302262110584e68 span,.c03456f3b4db1077ee302262110584e68 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
a:hover{
color:#ffffff;background:#ffc658!important;
}
.nav-link{
color: #000000;

}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar navbar-expand-lg">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/index.html"  ><img alt="img/logo.jpg" src="img/logo.jpg" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="navbar-collapse collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="d-flex ml-auto navbar-nav align-items-center"><li class="nav-item">
<a class="nav-link wee80a68dcaf500498d56521d846d3091" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/index.html" >rape attorney</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="wee80a68dcaf500498d56521d846d3091 nav-link" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/murder-attorney.html" >murder attorney</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="wee80a68dcaf500498d56521d846d3091 nav-link" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/drug-attorney.html" >drug attorney</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="nav-link wee80a68dcaf500498d56521d846d3091" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/criminal-lawyer-los-angeles.html" >criminal lawyer los angeles</a>
</li>
<li class="dropdown nav-item">
<a class="wee80a68dcaf500498d56521d846d3091 dropdown-toggle nav-link" href="#" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">More</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/criminal-lawyer-near-me.html"  >criminal lawyer near me</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/rape-lawyer.html"  >rape lawyer</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/murder-lawyer.html"  >murder lawyer</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/drug-lawyer.html"  >drug lawyer</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/domestic-violence-legal-support.html"  >Domestic Violence Legal Support</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/drug-crime-defense-strategies.html"  >Drug Crime Defense Strategies</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/sex-crime-defense-attorneys.html"  >Sex Crime Defense Attorneys</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/fraud-and-white-collar-crime-cases.html"  >Fraud and White-Collar Crime Cases</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/homicide-defense-attorneys.html"  >Homicide Defense Attorneys</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/federal-and-state-case-representation.html"  >Federal and State Case Representation</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/client-testimonials-and-case-results.html"  >Client Testimonials and Case Results</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/protecting-your-legal-rights.html"  >Protecting Your Legal Rights</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/the-criminal-trial-process.html"  >The Criminal Trial Process</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/defense-against-serious-charges.html"  >Defense Against Serious Charges</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/strategies-for-white-collar-crimes.html"  >Strategies for White-Collar Crimes</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/legal-insights-and-news.html"  >Legal Insights and News</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/emergency-legal-assistance.html"  >Emergency Legal Assistance</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/top-trial-attorneys-in-los-angeles.html"  >Top Trial Attorneys in Los Angeles</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/california-criminal-law-explained.html"  >California Criminal Law Explained</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/steps-to-building-your-defense.html"  >Steps to Building Your Defense</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/the-role-of-a-criminal-defense-attorney.html"  >The Role of a Criminal Defense Attorney</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/criminal-attorney.html"  >Criminal Attorney</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/criminal-lawyer.html"  >criminal lawyer</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/criminal-attorney-los-angeles.html"  >criminal attorney los angeles</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/criminal-attorney-near-me.html"  >criminal attorney near me</a></div>
</li>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="wee80a68dcaf500498d56521d846d3091 nav-link" rel=nofollow href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li></ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for Saffari Law Group</h1>
<p>At Saffari Law Group one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Saffari Law Group and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: https://saffarilawgroup.com/</p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Saffari Law Group. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, Saffari Law Group, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>Saffari Law Group follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Saffari Law Group.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Saffari Law Group, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that Saffari Law Group has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>Saffari Law Group's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>Saffari Law Group does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
Saffari Law Group</br>
</br>
</br>
</br>
</br>
https://saffarilawgroup.com/</br>
</br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="py-4 container pt-5" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3">
<p>Saffari Law Group</p>
<p>Company Website : <a class="wee80a68dcaf500498d56521d846d3091" href="https://saffarilawgroup.com/" rel="nofollow">https://saffarilawgroup.com/</a></p>
</div><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="wee80a68dcaf500498d56521d846d3091" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="wee80a68dcaf500498d56521d846d3091" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="wee80a68dcaf500498d56521d846d3091" href="https://criminalattorney.netlify.app/about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
</p>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
